I think it's up by the post, by the post office, so we should walk here and check him here,
so we're going to walk up there like that, alright, I'll walk on up, you're going to give me protection, from what, you still keep calling me,
I love so much about that video, I love the genuineness of their laughter, like, they're what I call blackling,
it's a cackle, but it's a blackle, because don't nobody cackle like black folks,
I love the comfort with which they're touching each other, they're hugging, they're pulling on each other, but it's relaxed,
and I love just the casualness with which they're acknowledging each other's strength,
you're going to protect me, well, I need to protect you, you suckly Carmichael,
which acknowledges to each other that we both know who we are, and what we are,
this is the legacy we're being left with, this is what I mean by our ancestors have left us,
not freedom, but a continued fight for it, this is what I mean when I say,
we are the continuance, not the culmination, rest in power to both of these brothers,
and may we aspire to continue the work that they have left us imbued with.